Inspired by a legend. Bound by a dream.
Song Sung Blue is a drama, music, romance film directed by Craig Brewer.
Based on a true story, two down-on-their-luck musicians form a joyous Neil Diamond
tribute band, proving it's never too late to find love and follow your dreams.
Mike Sardina, played by Hugh Jackman.
Claire Sardina, played by Kate Hudson.
Mark Shurilla, played by Michael Imperioli.
Dr. Dave Watson, played by Fisher Stevens.
Tom D'Amato, played by Jim Belushi.
Rachel, played by Ella Anderson.
Song Sung Blue is a 2025 American biographical musical drama film
written, co-produced, and directed by Craig Brewer.
It is based on the 2008 documentary film of the same name by Greg Kohs.
The film stars Hugh Jackman and Kate Hudson as Mike and Claire Sardina, who
performed as the Neil Diamond tribute band Lightning & Thunder.
Song Sung Blue had its premiere at the AFI Film Festival on October 26, 2025, and
was released in the United States by Focus Features on December 25.
The film received positive reviews from critics, with particular praise for Hudson's performance, garnering her
nominations for the Golden Globe Award, Actor Award, and the Academy Award for Best Actress.
The film explores themes of wisconsin, based on true story,
based on movie, milwaukee wisconsin, tribute band.
The tone is emotional.